<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="automated_seo.frequently_ask_questions" name="Frequently Asked Questions">
            <section class="container grid md:gap-6 grid-cols-1 md:grid-cols-11">
            <div class="md:col-span-3">
                <div class="side-sticky">
                    <h2 class="cont-padding">Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
                    <a href="#footer-form-id" class="text-h5 text-primary faq-head max-md:mt-sm">Still have questions? <span class="md:block">Let’s talk<span class="bg-rightarrowLineBlack"></span></span></a>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="md:col-span-8 faq-head-outer">
                <div class="accordian-outer">
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light" >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">What is Angular, and why should I use it for my project?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;">
                            <p itemprop="text">Angular is a robust, open-source web application framework by Google. It is designed to simplify the development and testing of SPAs, offering a robust structure and set of tools for creating dynamic and scalable projects. Angular offers features like two-way binding, dependency injection, and modular architecture, streamlining development processes and improving performance. It allows you to ensure a maintainable and efficient codebase, strong community support, and rich user interfaces.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light" >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">What kind of projects is Angular best suited for?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;" >
                            <p itemprop="text">Angular is best suited for large-scale, complex web solutions that require a solid foundation and high performance. It excels in projects that involve SPAs, enterprise-level apps, eCommerce platforms, real-time data apps, PWAs, and CMS.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light" >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">What is the difference between AngularJS and Angular?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;" >
                            <p itemprop="text">AngularJS (2010) is based on JavaScript, while Angular (2016) is a complete rewrite based on TypeScript. The main differences include architecture, where AngularJS uses a scope and controller-based system, and Angular adopts a component-based approach. Angular offers enhanced performance, faster load times, a more modular structure for easier management and scalability, and superior tooling support, including a powerful CLI, ahead-of-time compilation, and improved testing capabilities.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light" >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">Why should I migrate from AngularJS to Angular?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;">
                            <p itemprop="text">Migrating from AngularJS to Angular offers several benefits, such as Enhanced Performance, Better Tooling, Long-term Support, Modern Features, and more. This clearly signifies why you should migrate to Angular from AngularJS.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light" >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">Do your developers have experience with the latest Angular versions?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;">
                            <p itemprop="text">Yes, our developers are highly experienced with the latest versions of Angular. They continuously update their skills and knowledge to stay abreast of the latest advancements in the Angular ecosystem, ensuring your project benefits from the latest features, best practices, and performance improvements.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light"  >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">How much does it cost to hire Angular developers?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;">
                            <p itemprop="text">We offer simple and transparent pricing for hiring experienced AngularJS developers at $18 per hour, with an average of 3+ years of experience. Rates may vary based on your specific requirements and the developer's expertise. For team hires, we provide customized rates. Please contact us for more details.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light"  >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">When we hire AngularJS developers from Bacancy, will they help me complete my incomplete development project?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;">
                            <p itemprop="text">Absolutely. Our Angularjs developers can seamlessly take over and complete your incomplete app development. They will assess the current state of your project, identify any gaps or issues, and work efficiently to deliver a high-quality, finished product in record time.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="accordion-item accordian-tab bg-gray-light"  >
                        <div class="faq-heading">
                            <h3 class="font-bold text-dark text-base mb-0">Do you provide support and maintenance services after deployment?</h3>
                        </div>
                        <div class="accordian-text" style="display: none;" >
                            <p itemprop="text">Yes, we provide comprehensive support and maintenance services post-deployment to ensure your Angular system runs smoothly and remains up-to-date. Our services include bug fixes, performance optimization, feature enhancements, and regular updates to keep your Angular system secure and efficient.</p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
    </section>
        <script type="text/javascript" t-js="true">
            document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
                var accordionItems = document.querySelectorAll('.sidebar_right_outer .res-submenu, .sidebar_right_outer .res-submenu, .accordion-item .faq-heading');

                accordionItems.forEach(function(item) {
                    item.addEventListener('click', function() {
                        var parent = this.closest('.accordion-item');
                        var content = parent.querySelector('.accordian-text');
                        var allItems = document.querySelectorAll('.accordion-item');

                        allItems.forEach(function(otherItem) {
                            if (otherItem !== parent) {
                                otherItem.classList.remove('active');
                                var otherContent = otherItem.querySelector('.accordian-text');
                                if (otherContent) {
                                    otherContent.style.display = 'none';
                                }
                            }
                        });

                        parent.classList.toggle('active');
                        if (content) {
                            content.style.display = content.style.display === 'none' ? 'block' : 'none';
                        }
                    });
                });
            });
        </script>
    </template>
</odoo>